http://www.stephensons.com/privacy-and-cookie-policy

Menu
Essential COVID ProductsFood & Drink Packaging
Takeaway Cocktail Packaging
Clear Takeaway Containers & Snap On Lids
Takeaway & Home Delivery PackagingPizza BoxesBurger Takeaway Foil Food Takeaway Containers & LidsClear Takeaway Containers & Snap On Lids BePulp Containers, Bowls & LidsBepulp Sauce Pot & LidsBlack Fastpac Containers & LidsKraft & White Food CartonsPolystyrene Takeaway PackagingBagasse Takeaway PackagingTaste Food-To-Go BoxesCake Boxes & CasesRound Noodle BoxesRound Foam & Plastic Containers & LidsCarrier / Delivery BagsHome Compostable PackagingCompostable PackagingStreet Food PackagingNewsprint Street Food PackagingKraft Street Food PackagingWhite Street Food PackagingFestival Street Food PackagingPolystyrene Street Food PackagingBagasse Street Food PackagingWooden Bamboo Street Food PackagingCompostable Street Food PackagingUK Design Street Food PackagingEdenware Noir Street Food PackagingDeli, Cafe & Sandwich PackagingSandwich, Baguette & Wrap BoxesPanini, Toastie & Chips BagsSauce & Deli PotsBepulp Home Compostable Sauce Pot and LidsSoup ContainersSalad ContainersTakeaway Ice Cream TubsFood Platters & BowlsGreaseproof Paper & BagsTakeaway Carrier / Delivery BagsVest Carrier BagsKraft Paper Carrier BagsWhite Paper Carrier BagsKraft Carry PacksDelivery BagsDisposable Plates & CutleryPlates & BowlsDip PotsDisposable CutlerySkewersPaper Drinking StrawsPlastic Bendy StrawsPlastic Straight StrawsCompostable PLA StrawsBiodegradable Chitosan StrawsMetal StrawsPlastic GlassesDisposable Plastic Tumbler GlassesrPET Disposable Plastic GlassesPLA Disposable Plastic Glasses100% Recycled Accelerate Disposable GlassesBiodegradable Disposable Plastic GlassesPaper Cups CE MarkedAmerican Plastic Party CupsKaterglass Premium Disposable TumblersDisposable Plastic Shot GlassesDisposable Plastic Wine, Champagne & Martini GlassesDisposable Plastic Vending CupsTakeaway Cocktail PackagingTakeaway Cocktail Pouches & BottlesTakeaway Cocktail Tulip Shape Cups & LidsTakeaway Cocktail Straight Shape Cup & LidsTakeaway Coffee CupsWhite Single Wall Coffee Cups & LidsWhite Single Wall PLA Lined Coffee Cups & LidsVegware Eco-Friendly Double Walled Coffee Cups & LidsMatt Black Double Wall Coffee Cups & LidsEnjoy Double Wall Hot Cups & LidsKraft Triple Wall PLA Lined Coffee Cups & LidsBiodegradable Triple Wall Coffee CupsKraft Triple Wall Coffee Cups & LidsBlack Triple Wall Coffee Cups & LidsVending CupsPolystyrene Cups & LidsReusable Hot CupsChristmas Takeaway Coffee Cups & LidsCup Holders & DispensersSpoons & StirrersTakeaway Cold Cups & Smoothie CupsDrinks Takeaway AccessoriesNapkinsRecycled & Compostable NapkinsCocktail NapkinsLunch Napkins2 Ply Dinner Napkins3 Ply Dinner NapkinsTork Linstyle Airlaid Dinner Napkins 39cmDuni NapkinsFlag NapkinsNapkin DispenserCoastersTable Covers, Doyleys & PlacematsTable Covers & Banquet RollsPaper Doyleys & Tray CoversPlacemats & Tete-a-Tete Crockery
Porcelite Seasons
Steelite Craft
Cheap Catering CrockeryPure White Catering CrockerySimply WhitePorcelain Additional ItemsOrient Temptation PorcelainOrion Elements PorcelainContra Black PorcelainColoured Teapots & CupsBaristaBevandeGenware Coloured PorcelainPrice & Kensington Coloured Teapots & MugsStump Coloured TeapotsCeramic Coloured TeapotsPebble Coloured TeapotsMenu Shades Coloured BeverageSquashy MugsAcme & CoEnamelwareGenwareTerra StonewareTerra 'Each Piece Unique' PorcelainLuna Black StonewareUtopia TablewareRustico StonewareRustico Ironstone Stoneware Rustico Natura StonewareRustico Oxide StonewareRustico Vintage StonewareRustico Aztec StonewareRustico Impressions StonewarePorcelite Vitrified PorcelainPorcelite SeasonsPorcelite AuraPorcelite WhitewarePorcelite CreationsPorcelite PrestigePorland Perspective by PorcelitePorcelite Rustic Brown Oven to TablewarePorcelite Oven to TablewarePorcelite Buffet GastronormChurchill ChinaStonecast ColoursPlume - StonecastAqueous - StonecastPatina - StonecastHints - StonecastRaku - Studio PrintsRaku Centre Prints - Studio PrintsStone - Studio PrintsHomespun - Studio PrintsHaze Blue (Semi Matt Glaze) - Studio PrintsMineral - Studio PrintsAgano - Studio PrintsKintsugi - Studio PrintsBreccia & Fluid - Studio PrintsEmergeNourishBit On The SideBulbMonochromeVellum (Semi Matt Glaze)ProfileWhitewareUltimo Chefs' Plates CollectionEvolveOrbOrbitX SquaredBamboo WhiteBamboo ColoursIslaBlue WillowVintage PrintsRetro BlueArt de Cuisine by ChurchillSteeliteThe Potters Collection by Robert GordonAdelaide by Robert GordonSteelite Craft Steelite Craft RaspberrySteelite Charcoal DappleSteelite Blue DappleSteelite Brown DappleSteelite BeadSteelite Urban Steelite RevolutionSteelite VesuviusSteelite Ink LegacySteelite Ink CrackleSteelite Ink NomadSteelite AuroraSteelite FreestyleSteelite Simplicity WhiteSteelite TasteSteelite ScapeSteelite Monaco White Fine ChinaSteelite Willow Fine ChinaDudsonEvoEvo OriginsHarvestTerrazzoWhiteDenbyHaloStudio CraftStudio GreyBlue HazeModusStudio BlueImperial BlueAlchemy Fine ChinaVilleroy & BochRoyal Crown DerbySussex Fine Bone ChinaTafelstern & BauscherConnoisseur Fine Bone ChinaPorland Academy Fine ChinaImperial Fine ChinaSchonwald Premium PorcelainGlass Plates & BowlsPlastic TablewareOven to TablewareCrockery Washing & Storage Cutlery
Robert Welch 18/10 Cutlery
Villeroy & Boch 18/10 Cutlery
Economy 18/0 CutleryTraditional 18/0 Cutlery Contemporary 18/0 CutleryPremium 18/10 Cutlery Robert Welch 18/10 CutleryVilleroy & Boch 18/10 CutleryAmefa 18/10 CutleryAnton Black 18/10 CutleryArcoroc 18/10 CutleryArtis 18/10 CutleryChef & Sommelier 18/10 CutleryChurchill 18/10 CutlerySola Switzerland 18/10 CutleryElia 18/10 CutleryGrunwerg 18/10 CutleryPintinox 18/10 'Stone Washed' CutleryPintinox 18/10 CutlerySteelite 18/10 CutleryUtopia 18/10 CutleryChildrens CutlerySteak Knives & ForksPizza Cutlery & CuttersCheese KnivesLatte SpoonsSeafood CutlerySpecialist CutleryEscargotCoffee & TeaspoonsMeat / Sugar / Ice TongsPastry / Tea ForksButter KnivesIce Cream Spoon / ScoopsOriental Cuisine CutleryTasting CutleryVoluto SpoonsOther Specialist ItemsService CutleryStainless Steel Service ItemsEconomy Service ItemsPolycarbonate Service ItemsBlack Handled Service ItemsVilleroy & Boch Service ItemsRobert Welch Service ItemsColour Coded TongsWooden Salad ServersDisposable CutleryWrapped CutleryCPLA & Compostable CutleryWooden Disposable CutleryWhite Disposable CutleryClear Disposable CutleryBlack Disposable CutleryMetallic Disposable CutleryCopper Disposable CutleryMini Tasting Disposable CutleryToothpicks, Chopsticks, Stirrers & ScoopsPlastic Coloured CutleryAdapted CutleryCutlery HoldersCutlery Storage & CareFront of House
Bolsius Twilight Candles
Napkins
Food PresentationFood Serving Baskets Food Serving BucketsChip PresentationFood Serving TraysNaturally Med Olive Wood Bowls & BoardsWooden TablewareGlass JarsMini PansMiniature IdeasEnamelwareEagle Speckled EnamelwareAvebury Blue Stoneware CrockeryPresentation BoardsSlateMini Oven to TablewareCast IronSlide ControlFood Gun Smoker KilnerServing DishesCake & CheeseCake Cake StandsAfternoon High TeaCake DisplayCheese Cruets, Condiments & DipsSalt & Pepper ShakersSalt & Pepper MillsOil & VinegarShakers & PourersMini Jugs & SauceboatsRamekins & DipsGravy & Sauce Boats Squeezy Sauce BottlesTea & Coffee ServiceInsulated AirpotsInsulated Vacuum JugsPlastic Insulated Beverage ServersLarge Beverage DispensersStainless Steel Tea & Coffee WareCafétièresSpeciality TeaCast Iron TeapotsMilk & Juice Coffee Machines & AccessoriesManual Fill Water Boilers / Water UrnsKettlesBarista SuppliesBeverage AccessoriesWhite Ceramic Teapots, Coffee Pots, Jugs & Sugar Bowls Price & Kensington Coloured TeapotsStump TeapotsPebble TeapotsBevande Beverage CollectionReusable Stojo CupsReusable Rice Husk CupsTrays & TrolleysTrolleysTraysBuffet & Food DisplayChafing Dishes & FuelSoup Kettles & AccessoriesCake ServiceCold BeverageHot BeverageBreakfast ServiceMeat Flats & Vegetable DishesGastronorm & Hot Tiles1/3 Silicone Gastronorm 65mm DeepDeli Crocks & SaladMelamine BuffetwareDalebrook Melamine BuffetwareMarl 'Stoneware Effect' Melamine CollectionMarl Blue Steel MelamineMarl Cream MelamineMarl Charcoal Grey MelamineMineral 'Crackle' Glaze Effect Melamine CollectionMineral Noir MelamineMineral Aqua MelamineMineral Indigo MelamineMineral Parchment MelamineMineral Agate Grey MelaminePigment 'Matt Effect' Melamine CollectionOmni 'Health Care' Melamine CollectionOmni Healthcare Melamine Low PlatesOmni Healthcare Melamine Deep PlatesOmni Healthcare Melamine BowlsOmni Healthcare Melamine Cups and SaucersOmni Healthcare Melamine MugsTura 'Paint Effect' Melamine CollectionTura 'Paint Effect' Melamine TraysTura 'Paint Effect' Melamine CrocksOxford Melamine PlattersBamboo Trays and Melamine InsertsGastronorm Melamine PlattersAcrylic BuffetwareZieherRosseto Buffet Serving SolutionsGlass BuffetwareWooden BuffetwareCeramic BuffetwareBuffet Platters & TraysBuffet UtensilsBuffet RisersBuffet StandsBuffet NoticesCandles & HoldersNightlight & Tealight CandlesBolsius Twilight CandlesBolsius Relight Candle Holders & RefillsBolsius Starlight Jar CandlesAltar CandlesTapered CandlesCandle HoldersBattery Operated CandlesLightersTablecloths, Napkins & MatsHigh Chairs & Banqueting FurnitureInternational / World CuisineMexicanEscargot & Seafood ServiceEthnic Food ServiceMediterraneanFood BasketsChildren's Dining Childrens DisposablesMenus & Order TakingTill RollsService to the TableDuni Sealable & Long SacchettosWrapped Disposable Cutlery & PacksPlate Covers Tray StandsTraysSignage & DisplayPeg BoardsLetter ShelvesFood Allergen SignageMenu & Notice DisplayChalkboards & MarkersSecurit Water Soluble Chalk Marker Pens with Small 1-2mm NibBarrier Posts & RopesBar SignageDoor SignsTable SignsOutdoor SignageHotel & B&BOpening Hours SignageTable Signs & DisplaySignage New LaunchesThe Copper TrendHousekeepingToiletriesJust For YouSloane StreetTaylor of LondonGojoLockable Dispensers & RefillsBathroom AccessoriesToilet HygieneFeminine HygieneBath Mats & Shower CurtainsVanity Kits, Shower Caps & SlippersWaste BinsSignsBedroom AccessoriesIrons & Ironing BoardsCoat Hangers, Door Signs & Sewing KitsBedroom TumblersLuggage RacksHairdryersKettles & Coffee MachinesWelcome Trays & Ice BucketsTissue HoldersBedroom BinsGuest Information FoldersMini Bar Fridges & SafesMini Bar FridgesSafesServiced Apartment KitchensWashing UpCutleryKitchen UtensilsMeasuring Jugs, Mixing Bowls & ColandersBaking TraysPan Sets & Frying PansCondimentsKitchen Roll HoldersDomestic ElectricalsFront of House New LaunchesGlassware
Gin & Tonic Glasses
Hobstar Glass Tumblers by Artis
Beer GlassesCraft Beer GlassesBeer Growlers & Take Out CarriersBeer Tankards Pint & Half Pint GlassesThird and Two Thirds of a Pint GlassesBranded Beer GlassesTall Glasses for Bottled BeerStemmed Beer GlassesTumblersValue TumblersToughened TumblersStandard TumblersPremium TumblersColoured TumblersVintage Style TumblersCrystal TumblersBranded TumblersWine GlassesWine Glasses Ideal for HomeValue Wine GlassesToughened Wine GlassesPremium Wine GlassesVilleroy & Boch GlasswareWine Tasting GlassesGin & Tonic GlassesChampagne Flutes & SaucersCocktail GlassesMartini GlassesMargarita Cocktail GlassesStemmed Cocktail GlassesTall Cocktail GlassesBeer Cocktail GlassesAbsinthe GlassesCocktail SaucersVintage Cocktail GlassesTraditional Mojito GlassesFish Bowl CocktailsTiki Cocktail GlassesScience Cocktail GlassesCocktail MugsCocktail Cans, Cartons & Julep CupsCocktail BottlesCocktail Drinking JarsCocktail Drinks Dispensers & BarrelsLa Rochere Abeille Bee Cocktail GlassesCocktail TumblersMetal Cocktail GlassesGarden Themed Cocktails Coffee Cocktail GlassesMini Cocktail GlassesSharing Cocktail GlassesReusable Plastic Cocktail GlassesShot GlassesSherry, Port & Liqueur GlassesBrandy & Whisky Tasting GlassesCoffee GlassesSundaes & DessertsExtra Large GlasswareColoured GlasswareJugs, Carafes, Bottles & DecantersDisposable Plastic Glasses Disposable Plastic Glasses & Lid to FitDisposable Beer Glasses Takeaway Paper Beer Glasses CE2 Pint / 1 Ltr Drink OptionsDisposable Plastic TumblersPLA Disposable Plastic TumblersBiodegradable Plastic GlassesKaterglass Premium Disposable GlassesDisposable Smoothie Cups & LidsDisposable PLA Smoothie Cups & LidsDisposable Plastic Wine, Champagne & Cocktail GlassesDisposable Plastic ShotsDisposable Vending CupsReusable Plastic Glasses Reusable Beer GlassesReusable 2 Pint Plastic Beer Glasses Premium Reusable Plastic GlassesReusable Plastic TumblersElite Remedy Polycarbonate Plastic Reusable TumblersPlastic Serving JugsReusable Plastic Gin & Tonic GlassesPremium Reusable Plastic Wine & Champagne GlassesReusable Plastic Shot GlassesBlack & White Coloured Plastic GlassesHarfield Plastic TumblersStorage & CareBar Equipment
Monin
Bar Trays
Straws & StirrersStrawsDrink Stirrers & SparklersCoastersCocktail Napkins & Bar CaddiesCocktail NapkinsBar CaddiesBar TraysMeasures & PourersOpeners & ResealersCocktail EquipmentCocktail Glass & Can ShakersMixing GlassesCocktail StrainersCocktail Mixing SpoonsMuddlersCocktail JiggersCocktail Making KitsCopper Plated BarwareGun Metal BarwareVintage Steel BarwareAntique Brass BarwareGold BarwareFruit Squeezers, Wedgers, Boards & CuttersJuice Storers & Speed RailsCondiment DispensersDash & Bitter BottlesMister BottleIce Trays,Crushers & PicksCream Whippers, Soda Syphons & BlowlampsBartender Training & Cocktail BookSmoking GunCocktail Syrups, Purees & MixersMoninODKCocktail MixersLemon / Lime / Garnish PreparationKnives & WedgersBar Cutting BoardsFruit ZestersLemon & Lime SqueezersCondiment DispensersFruit BasketsWine/Champagne Coolers & BucketsWine CoolersIce Buckets, Tongs & ScoopsChampagne CoolersWine / Champagne Buckets & StandsBeer BucketsGlass Care & StorageBottle Collection & SkipsTubtrugs For Bottle CollectionBottle SkipsBar Mats & Floor MattingBar MatsDrip TraysFloor MattingEntrance MattingArtificial GrassBar Signage & DisplayBar SignageChalkboards & MarkersPeg BoardsNotice / Menu DisplayOutdoor SignageEquipmentSpindle Drinks MixersJuicers & Ice CrushersBartender SpherificatorBar Heavy EquipmentBar BlendersBar AccessoriesBar GamesCellar EquipmentAshtraysFurnitureKitchen Equipment
Allergen Kitchen Equipment
Pizza Equipment
Chefs' Knives & AccessoriesUtensilsBBQ ToolsCorers, Ballers & CurlersEgg Slicers, Toppers and RingsPlastic & Stainless Steel FunnelsIce Cream Scoops & PortionersLadlesLighters & Blow TorchesMashers & TenderisersPeelersPizza WheelsPrecision Preparation ToolsScissors & ShearsServing Spoons & SpoodlesSkewers & Meat HooksScoopsSkimmers, Chip Scoops & LiftersSpatulasTongsTurners & ScrapersUtensil Hanging RailUtensils for Non-Stick CookwareWhisksWooden & Plastic SpoonsZesters & Canelle KnivesOther UtensilsFood PreparationMoulinsVegetable Cutters & ChippersMandolinesChopping BoardsGraters Ricer & MincerMeat & Fish PreparationKitchen ScalesColandersChinois, Sieves & StrainersFunnelsMeasuring Jugs / CupsMixing BowlsPudding BasinsCream WhippersPasta & SpaghettiHandee Cheese SlicersKitchen Sauce & Condiment DispensersSalad SpinnersKitchen BucketsCan OpenersPastry & BakewarePastry & Baking PreparationBakewarePastry & Bakeware ServiceCookwareBaking Sheets & Roasting PansFrying PansOmelette, Blinis & Paella PansSauteuse & Sauce PansStainless Steel Casseroles & Stock PotsAluminium Casseroles & Stock PotsWoksSpecialist CookwareGriddles & Sizzle PlattersOven to TablewareGastronormStainless Steel GastronormGastronorm AccessoriesClear Polycarbonate GastronormBlack Polycarbonate GastronormAraven Translucent GastronormStewart Translucent Gastronorm Containers with Seal Tight LidsVollrath Super Shape Stainless Steel GastronormFlexepan Silicone GastronormAraven Silicone Gastronorm LidsStorage & ContainersGeneral Food Storage Containers / BinsStewart Sealfresh ContainersAraven Storage ContainersAraven Anti-Allergen Food ContainersPolycarbonate Food Storage ContainersButchers' TraysPrepared Food StorageTubtrugs - Perfect For Food Storage & Prep.Food Storage BagsFood TransportationKANGA Storage BoxesScoopsAllergen Kitchen EquipmentThermometersKitchen OrderPizza EquipmentDay Dots, Date & Allergen LabelsDay Dot Rotation Labels & DispensersDissolving Day Rotation Food Labels & DispenserTrilingual Day Rotation Labels & DispenserThrow Away On Food Label & DispenserDate & Data Labels & GunUse By Date Labels & GunAllergen LabelsVegetarian & Vegan Food LabelsShelf Life, Use By, Sous Vide Labels & DispenserKitchen DisposablesWrapmasterCatering Cling FilmCatering FoilBaking ParchmentGreaseproof SheetsPicks, Skewers, Steak Markers & Cutlet FrillsSouffle CupsCatering WipesFilter PapersToothpicksAppliancesPaper Hygiene
Blue Roll
Blue RollCentrefeed Rolls & DispenserDomestic Kitchen Roll & HoldersIndustrial BumperollTork ReflexHand TowelsC-fold Hand Towels & DispensersZ-fold Hand Towels & DispensersPremium Washroom HandtowelTork Xpress Multifold H2 Hand Towel SystemTork Matic H1 Hand Towel SystemLeonardo Hand Roll SystemsLeonardo Hand Towel SystemsToilet RollsMini Jumbo Toilet RollTork SmartOne Toilet Roll SystemJumbo Toilet RollTork SmartOne Mini Toilet Roll SystemBulk Pack Toilet TissueTork Advanced Mini Jumbo Toilet Roll SystemDomestic Toilet RollTork Twin Mid-Size Toilet Roll SystemTork Coreless Mid-Size Toilet Roll SystemLeonardo Versatwin Toilet Roll SystemFacial Tissues & WipesCleaning
Alcohol Gel & Dispensers
Kitchen Cleaning Chemicals
Hand HygieneAlcohol Gel & DispensersKitchen HandcareWashroom HandcareGojo & PurellSoap For Hand WashingSoap Dispensers & CartridgesWall Mounted Refillable Soap Dispensers Floor Standing Refillable Soap DispensersHand Basins & Mobile Sinks Now Wash Your Hands StickersVirucidal Sprays, Soaps & StationsVirucidal / Antibacterial Cleaning WipesVirucidal
/ Disinfecting Sprays & RefillsDisinfection ULV Sprayer / FoggerCleaning ChemicalsKitchen Cleaning ChemicalsWashroom Cleaning ChemicalsHousekeeping Cleaning ChemicalsAir Fresheners & DeodorisersFurniture & Metal CareMachine Dish & Glass WashingBar & CellarFloor Cleaning & CareLaundrySpecialist Chemicals & CleanersLow Cost Arma Cleaning ChemicalsOptimum Hygiene Cleaning ChemicalsOptimum Holistic Green R P Adam Ltd Cleaning ChemicalsBio-Productions Cleaning ProductsHG Cleaning ChemicalsRational Oven Cleaning Cloths & ScourersDisposable Catering WipesScourersScotch-Brite Pads & ScourersDishclothsTea Towels, Glasscloths & Serving ClothsMulti Purpose ClothsEnvirolite Multi Surface ClothsDustersHotel Room ToiletriesSpa Range Toiletries Prime Range ToiletriesGilchrist & Soames ToiletriesThe Collection Range ToiletriesGloves & WorkwearDisposable Blue Vinyl Powder Free GlovesDisposable Blue Vinyl Powdered GlovesDisposable Clear Polythene GlovesDisposable Clear Vinyl Powder Free GlovesDisposable White Latex Powder Free GlovesDisposable White Latex Powdered GlovesDisposable Blue Nitrile Powder Free GlovesDisposable Black Nitrile Powder Free GlovesDisposable Blue PLA Powder Free GlovesRubber GlovesMulti-purpose GlovesOven GlovesCatering Cleaning ApronsWorkwearHousekeepingGriddle CleaningBrushes & SqueegeesMops & BucketsStandard Mops & BucketsKentucky Mops & BucketsOther Mopping ItemsColour Coded CleaningYellow - Front Of HouseBlue - KitchenRed - ToiletsGreen - OutdoorWaste ManagementBin Bags BinsCigarette Bins & AshtraysRecyclingJanitorial AccessoriesElectrical Cleaning EquipmentVacuum CleanersBuffing MachinesFly KillersHealth & Safety
PPE
Social Distancing & Queue Control
PPEFace Masks Fabric Face MasksFace VisorsBumpaa Antiviral SnoodsFace Covering SignsApronsOther PPE ItemsHeadwearHigh VisibilityHearing ProtectionFire Safety SignsCaution & Warning SignsNo Access & Prohibition SignsHealth & Safety Law PosterSmokingSafety & First Aid Guidance PostersCOSHH Regulation NoticeWashroom SignsKitchen SignsKitchen Signage PacksHand Hygiene SignageGeneral Kitchen NoticesFood Preparation SignageFood Storage SignageKitchen Memo Boards & PensFood Allergen Signs & LabelsFood Allergen LabelsFood Allergen PicksFood Allergen Wall & Table NoticesFood Allergen Buffet NoticesEnergy Saving and Recycling SignsFood LabelsDay Dot Labels & DispensersDissolving Day Rotation Labels & DispenserTrilingual Item / Date / Use By Labels & DispenserThrow Away Day Labels & DispenserDate & Data Labels & GunUse By Date Labels & GunAllergy LabelsUse First, Shelf Life & Sous Vide Labels & DispenserFood Temperature ControlFirst AidFly ControlQueue ManagementSocial Distancing & Queue ControlSocial Distancing Seat Markers1m Social Distancing Outside Vinyl BannersSocial Distancing Pull Up Roller BannerClothing
Disposable & Plastic Bib Aprons
Chef Jackets
Chef JacketsChef TrousersCatering ApronsDisposable & Plastic Bib ApronsChef's Bib ApronsChefs Bib ApronsChef Works Dorset Chef's Bib ApronChef's Waist ApronsFront Of House Bib ApronsFront Of House Waist ApronsKids' Bib ApronsKids' Full Bib ApronsFront of House Shirts Polo ShirtsT-ShirtsHospitality TrousersWaistcoats & TiesHats, Caps & Hair NetsNecktiesShoes & ClogsWaiters Gloves & Serving ClothsTunics & TabardsLab CoatsHigh VisibilityLockersBlankets for Restaurants & BarsChristmas
Christmas Hot Cups & Lids
Christmas Catering Crackers
Christmas Catering Crackers** Crackers Available for Immediate Dispatch **Eco-Charity CrackersValue 9" Christmas CrackersClassic 10" Christmas CrackersClassic 11" Christmas CrackersClassic 12" Christmas CrackersDeluxe 14" Christmas CrackersChristmas Catering NapkinsHot Drink Machines & AccessoriesChristmas PartywareChristmas Catering Candles & HoldersChristmas Hot Cups & LidsChristmas Meal BoxesClearance
Clearance Sale
Clearance SaleChefware ClearanceKitchen ClearanceClearance MiscellaneousSteelite ClearanceACME ClearancePorcelite / DPS ClearanceTableware ClearanceCrockery ClearanceDisposable ClearanceCutlery ClearanceGlassware ClearanceDudson Tableware ClearanceDudson Clearance Classic WhiteDudson Clearance Classic White PlatesDudson Clearance Classic White Oval PlattersDudson Clearance Classic White GeometrixDudson Clearance Classic White CurveDudson Clearance Classic White Rectangular TraysDudson Clearance Classic White Soup / Pasta PlatesDudson Clearance Classic White BowlsDudson Clearance Classic White Cups & SaucersDudson Clearance Classic White BeverageDudson Clearance Classic White Tabletop ItemsDudson Clearance Classic White Sauce & Gravy BoatsDudson Clearance HarvestDudson Clearance Harvest Rectangular TraysDudson Clearance Harvest Chefs' BowlsDudson Clearance Harvest Large BowlsDudson Clearance Harvest Dip PotsDudson Clearance EvoDudson Clearance Evo Coupe PlatesDudson Clearance Evo Deep Coupe PlatesDudson Clearance Evo Chefs' Rectangular TraysDudson Clearance Evo BowlsDudson Clearance Evo Tabletop ItemsDudson Clearance Evo Cups & SaucersDudson Clearance Fine ChinaDudson Clearance Fine China ChamonixDudson Clearance Fine China MiscellaneousDudson Clearance MiscellaneousDudson Clearance Concrete Plates
Account
0161 483 6256
Find Us
We are OpenOur Cash & Carry is open for browsing.
Established since 1868We constantly benchmark our prices!
Home
Privacy and Cookie Policy
Privacy and Cookie Policy
H.G. Stephenson LimitedPrivacy Policy
H.G. Stephenson Limited (“Stephensons”) respect your privacy and are committed to protecting your personal data. In this privacy policy, we explain how we collect and use your personal information when you visit our website, or buy or use our products or services.
“We” are H.G. Stephenson Limited (company number 00065741) and we’re based at Kennerley Works, 161 Buxton Road, Stockport, Cheshire SK2 6EQ. We are the data controller for the purposes of the Data Protection Act 2018, the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and any other data protection legislation applicable in the UK from time to time.
If you have any questions about your privacy on our website, www.stephensons.com (“our website”), or our use of your personal data, please do not hesitate to Contact Us.
Please note that links from our website may take you to external websites which are not covered by this policy. We recommend that you check their privacy policies before submitting any personal information to such sites. We will not be responsible for the content, function or information collection policies of these external websites.
What information do we collect about you and how do we collect it?
You are not required (by law or by any contract with us) to provide personal information to us via our website. We will only require you to provide personal information to us where it is necessary for us to provide you with a service at your request.
Information you provide to us
We may receive personal information about you whenever you Contact Us. For example, by doing the following:
Enquiring about our products or services, including when you request a catalogue.
Purchasing our products or services.
Supplying us with your products or services.
Using and browsing our website.
Creating an account with us through our website.
Signing up to our newsletter.
Telephoning, texting, writing by post or emailing us.
Enquiring about, or applying for, job vacancies.
This information may include the following:
Normal identification information, such as your full name, date of birth, age, gender, marital status.
Contact information, such as your postal address, email address and telephone number.
Additional information relevant to your use of our website and services, such as your marketing preferences, survey responses and feedback.
Information about your shipment, including the recipient.
Your VAT status (for international shipments).
Payment information (this is securely collected and processed by our payment provider).
In respect of job applications, your CV including details of your education and employment history (and any other information which you may choose to provide to us with your CV).
Information we collect about you on our website
We collect information using cookies and other similar technologies to help distinguish you from other users of our website. These can streamline your online experience by saving you from re-inputting some information and also allow us to make improvements to our website. For more information about how and why we use cookies, please take a look through our Cookie Policy.
When you visit our website we may collect the following information:
Which pages you view and which links you follow.
Your IP address and general location.
Details of the hardware and software that you are using to access the website.
Any passwords that you use on our website.
If you choose to log in using a third party, we will record your login provider.
If you choose to link your account to a third party marketplace to import items for shipment, we will record the details necessary to facilitate that link.
A device identifier (cookie or IP address) for fraud prevention.
Details of your visits to our website and the resources that you access, including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data.
Where orders originate from advertising sources, we record the source of each order. This is purely to allow us to assess the effectiveness of these adverts and is not used for customer profiling of any kind.
Our website is not intended for children and we do not knowingly collect data relating to children.
Information we collect about you from other sources
We may collect information about you from other sources. This may include the following:
Publicly available information, from sources such as Companies House and the Electoral Roll.
Information you have shared publicly, including on social media (particularly in respect of job applications).
If you apply for a job, we may collect information about your criminal record by obtaining a DBS check through an approved agency (where required or permitted by law).
Information from third party databases or lead suppliers, such as credit reference agencies, including details about your home.
This list is not exhaustive and, in specific instances, we may need to collect additional data for the purposes set out in this policy.
Information we receive about you from other sources
Sometimes you will have given your consent for other websites, services or third parties to provide information to us.
This could include information we receive about you if you use any of the other websites that we operate or the other services that we provide, in which case we will have informed you when we collected that data if we intend to share those data internally and combine it with data collected on this website. We will also have told you for what purpose we will share and combine your data.
It could also include information from third parties that we work with to provide our products and services, such as payment processors, credit check facilities, delivery companies, technical support companies and advertising companies. Whenever we receive information about you from these third parties, we will let you know what information we have received and how and why we intend to use it.
How and why do we use your personal information?
We take data protection law seriously, so below we have set out exactly how and why we use your information, and what our legal basis is to be able to use your information in each way.
Supplying our products and providing our services
It is necessary for us to use personal information about you to enter into and perform the contracts that we make with you, such as when you become a customer. To process your personal data in this way, we will rely on legal bases of performing our contract with you and pursuing our legitimate interests. Using your information in this context is necessary so that we can:
Provide you with information about your contract with us.
Provide you with information about our products and services, including sending our monthly newsletter if you sign up to receive it.
Verify your identity.
Make a decision to supply our products and services.
Deal with any complaints you may have.
Contact you about any changes that we make to our products or services.
Administer our website, including troubleshooting problems, analysing statistics, conducting research and tests and keeping the website secure.
Administer your order and take payments.
If you enquire about, or apply for, a job vacancy, it is necessary for us to use your personal information as part of the recruitment process, in order to assess your suitability for a particular role.
Telling you about other products or services that we think may be of interest to you
We may use your information to identify and tell you about our products or services that we think may be of interest to you, and we will rely on the lawful basis of legitimate interests in doing so. We will only do this where you have informed us that you would like to receive marketing communications and you may update your preferences at any time by Contacting Us.
We may also use your information to invite you to participate in market research. If we do contact you about market research, you do not have to participate. If you tell us that you do not want to receive market research communications, we will respect this.
Whether you choose to receive marketing communications, or market research communications is entirely up to you. You can choose to receive both, none, or just one or the other. Your choice will not affect any products or services that you have purchased from us, nor will it affect any quotes for products or services you buy in future.
Telling you about products or services that are similar to ones that you have already bought
If you have already bought a product or service from us, or you have already obtained a quote from us, we may contact you with some information about products and services that are similar. We will rely on the lawful basis of legitimate interests in doing so.
We will only contact you by email or telephone and you can choose not to receive these messages at any time. Simply follow the instructions in the message, or Contact Us.
Making our business better
We always want to offer the best products, services and experience that we can. Sometimes this means we may use your information to find ways that we can improve what we do, or how we do it. For example, we may carry out email and postal campaigns and we may ask you for product and service reviews through our reviews platform.
In this context, we will rely on the lawful basis of legitimate interests and will only use your information where it is necessary so that we can:
Review and improve our existing products and services and develop new ones.
Review and improve the performance of our systems, processes and staff (including training).
Improve our website to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
Measure and understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you.
Contacting you
We want to stay in touch with you. Sometimes we may need to use the information that we have about you in order to respond to your questions or let you know about important changes. We will rely on the lawful basis of performing our contract with you and pursing our legitimate interests when we contact you.
We will only use your information in this respect where it is necessary so that we can:
Interact and respond to any communications you send us, including where you use the Contact Us section, and any social media posts that you tag us in.
Let you know about any important changes to our business or policies.
Verifying your identity
We may use your information where it is necessary for us to do so in order to meet our legal obligations or to detect and prevent fraud, money-laundering and other crimes.
Protecting you and others from harm
We may use your information where it is necessary to protect your interests, or the interests of others, in accordance with our legal obligations and the pursuit of legitimate interests. This may include in the event of criminality such as identity theft, piracy or fraud.
We need all the categories of information listed above to allow us:
(i)             to enter into and perform our contract with you;
(ii)            to enable us to comply with legal obligations; and
(iii)           to pursue legitimate interests of our own or those of third parties (provided your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests).
Change of purpose
We will only use your personal information for the purposes for which we collected it, unless we reasonably consider that we need to use it for another reason and that reason is compatible with the original purpose. If we need to use your personal information for an unrelated purpose we will notify you and we will explain the legal basis which allows us to do so.
Please note that we may process your personal information without your knowledge or consent, in compliance with the above rules, where this is required or permitted by law.
Who do we share your personal information with?
Sharing your information within our company and group
We share the information that you provide to us with our staff so that we can provide our products and services to you.
We may share the information that you provide to us with other companies within our group and other websites that we and our group companies operate.
Sharing your information with third parties
We may share your data with selected third parties. For example, we may share your information with:
Internet hosting providers to host the website, related infrastructure, services and applications.
Contact management systems to send emails, instant messages, social media messages and SMS messages.
Mailing distributor to send out catalogues or special offers.
Customer review platforms.
Payment gateway platforms.
There are certain exceptional circumstances in which we may disclose your information to third parties. This would be where we believe that the disclosure is:
Required by the law, or in order to comply with judicial proceedings, court orders or legal or regulatory proceedings.
Necessary to protect the safety of our employees, our property or the public.
Necessary for the prevention or detection of crime, including exchanging information with other companies or organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
Proportionate as part of a merger, business or asset sale, in the event that this happens we will share your information with the prospective seller or buyer involved.
How long do we keep your personal information?
We will only store your personal information for as long as we need it for the purposes for which it was collected. Where we provide you with any service, we will retain any information you provide to us at least for as long as we continue to provide that service to you.
If your application for employment is unsuccessful, the organisation will hold your data on file for 12 months after the end of the relevant recruitment process for consideration for future employment opportunities. At the end of that period, or once you withdraw your consent, your data will be deleted or destroyed.
We will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal accounting, or reporting requirements. To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements. In some circumstances, we may anonymise your personal data (so that it can no longer be associated with you) for research or statistical purposes in which case we may use this information indefinitely without further notice to you.
How do we protect your personal information?
We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this policy.
We try to ensure that all information you provide to us is transferred securely via the website. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our website; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.
All information you provide to us is stored on third party secure servers in the UK. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.
What rights do you have in respect of your personal information?
If you require any further information about your rights as explained below, or if you would like to exercise any of your rights, please Contact Us.
You have the right to be informed
We have a legal obligation to provide you with concise, transparent, intelligible and easily accessible information about your personal information and our use of it. We have written this policy to comply with this right.
You have the right to access your personal data
You have the right to ask us to confirm whether or not we hold any of your personal information. If we do, you have the right to have a copy of your information and to be informed of the following:
Why we have been using your information.
What categories of information we were using.
Who we have shared the information with.
How long we envisage holding your information.
In order to maintain the security of your information, we will have to verify your identity before we provide you with a copy of the information we hold. The first copy of your information that you request from us will be provided free of charge, if you require further copies we may charge an administrative fee to cover our costs.
You have the right to correct any inaccurate or incomplete personal data
Where you have requested a copy of the information we hold about you, you may notice that there are inaccuracies in the records, or that certain parts are incomplete. If this is the case you can Contact Us so that we can correct our records.
You have the right to be forgotten
There may be times where it is no longer necessary for us to hold personal information about you. This could be if:
The information is no longer needed for the original purpose that we collected it for.
You withdraw your consent for us to use the information (and we have no other legal reason to keep using it).
You object to us using your information and we have no overriding reason to keep using it.
We have used your information unlawfully.
We are subject to a legal requirement to delete your information.
In those situations you have the right to have your personal data deleted. If you believe one of these situations applies to you, please Contact Us.
You have the right to have your data transferred to you or a third party in a common format
Also known as data portability, you have the right to obtain a copy of your personal data for your own purposes. This right allows you to move, copy or transfer your personal data more easily from one IT system to another, in a safe and secure way.
If you would like us to transfer a copy of your data to you or another organisation in a structured, commonly use and machine-readable format, please Contact Us. There is no charge for you exercising this right.
You have the right to object to direct marketing
You can tell us at any time that you would prefer that we do not use your information for direct marketing purposes. If you would not like to receive any direct marketing from us, please Contact Us or use the links provided in any of our marketing communications.
You have the right to object to us using your information for our own legitimate interests
Sometimes, we use your personal information to achieve goals that will help us as well as you. This includes when we tell you about products or services that are similar to ones you have already bought; when we use your information to help us make our business better; and when we contact you to interact, communicate or to let you know about changes we are making.
We aim to always ensure that your rights and information are properly protected. If you believe that the way we are using your data is not justified due to its impact on you or your rights, you have the right to object. Unless we have a compelling reason to continue, we must stop using your personal data for these purposes.
You have the right to restrict how we use your personal data
You have the right to ask us to stop using your personal data in any way other than simply keeping a copy of it. This right is available where:
You have informed us that the information we hold about you is inaccurate, and we have not yet been able to verify this.
You have objected to us using your information for our own legitimate interests and we are in the process of considering your objection.
We have used your information in an unlawful way, but you do not want us to delete your data.
We no longer need to use the information, but you need it for a legal claim.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
Any changes we make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by email. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy.
This version was last updated on [INSERT DATE OF UPLOAD] and historic versions can be obtained by contacting us.
Complaints
If you wish to make a complaint about our collection or use of your personal data, please Contact Us in the first instance so that we may seek to resolve your complaint.
You have the right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO), the statutory body which oversees data protection law in the UK. Please visit the ICO website if you wish to lodge a complaint with the ICO.
Contact Us
All of our contact details are listed below.
